<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flexkube</title>
    <link>https://flexkube.github.io/documentation/guides/etcd/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Flexkube</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://flexkube.github.io/documentation/guides/etcd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://flexkube.github.io/documentation/guides/etcd/creating-multi-member-cluster-over-ssh-using-terraform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flexkube.github.io/documentation/guides/etcd/creating-multi-member-cluster-over-ssh-using-terraform/</guid>
      <description>Creating multi-member cluster over SSH using Terraform This guide describes how to create multi member etcd cluster using Terraform and Flexkube provider. The process is very simple and requires just a few steps. If you have at least 3 members, your cluster will be able to tolerate loss on one member, so it will be highly available.
Requirements For this guide, it is required to have at least 2 Linux machines, with Docker daemon installed and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://flexkube.github.io/documentation/guides/etcd/creating-single-member-cluster-on-local-machine-using-flexkube-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flexkube.github.io/documentation/guides/etcd/creating-single-member-cluster-on-local-machine-using-flexkube-cli/</guid>
      <description>Creating single-node etcd cluster on local machine using &amp;ldquo;flexkube&amp;rdquo; CLI This guide describes how to create single member etcd cluster using flexkube CLI. It will explain cluster creation process step by step to explain the configuration and provide some insights.
For fully automated creation, see Creating single-member etcd cluster on local machine using Terraform.
Requirements For this guide, it is required to have one Linux machine, with Docker daemon installed and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://flexkube.github.io/documentation/guides/etcd/creating-single-member-cluster-on-local-machine-using-terraform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flexkube.github.io/documentation/guides/etcd/creating-single-member-cluster-on-local-machine-using-terraform/</guid>
      <description>Creating single-member cluster on local machine using Terraform This guide describes how to create single member etcd cluster using Terraform and Flexkube provider. The process is very simple and requires just a few steps.
For more detailed guide, see Creating single member etcd cluster on local machine using flexkube CLI.
Requirements For this guide, it is required to have one Linux machine, with Docker daemon installed and running.
It is recommended that machine has at least 1 GB of RAM and is a fresh machine, as in tutorial the tools will write to directories like /var/lib/etcd or /etc/kubernetes/without notice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>